[
    {
        "question": "In St. Louis, Missouri, it`s illegal for a firefighter to rescue whom?",
        "answer": "Undressed women (even if they are wearing a nightgown)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was banned in Indonesia for `stimulating passion`?",
        "answer": "Hula hoops"
    },
    {
        "question": "In June in Wyoming, it is illegal to take a picture of what?",
        "answer": "A rabbit"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is banned in public places in Florida after 6 pm on a Thursday?",
        "answer": "Flatulence (farting)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to Russian law, a homeless person must be where after 10 pm?",
        "answer": "At home"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is illegal to eat with a cherry pie in Kansas?",
        "answer": "Ice cream"
    },
    {
        "question": "Vatican City and what other country have square flags?",
        "answer": "Switzerland"
    },
    {
        "question": "What nation has had its own scandals dubbed `Muldergate` and `Inkathagate`?",
        "answer": "South Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "What`s the official state sport of Alaska?",
        "answer": "Dog mushing"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the oldest bridge over the river Seine in Paris?",
        "answer": "Pont Neuf"
    },
    {
        "question": "Pont Neuf is the oldest bridge over the river Seine, located in which French city?",
        "answer": "Paris"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where would you find the Pont Neuf bridge?",
        "answer": "Paris, France"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which French city would you find the Pont Neuf bridge?",
        "answer": "Paris"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which continent are the Balkans a part of?",
        "answer": "Europe"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of the Netherlands?",
        "answer": "Amsterdam"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the Parthenon located?",
        "answer": "Greece"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Ontario?",
        "answer": "Toronto"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Estonia?",
        "answer": "Tallinn"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Egypt?",
        "answer": "Cairo"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which U.S. states does the Natchez Trace Parkway join?",
        "answer": "Mississippi and Tennessee -- It begins in Natchez, Mississippi, and ends near Nashville, Tennessee. It generally follows a trail once used by the Choctaw, Natchez, and Chickasaw."
    },
    {
        "question": "On what Norwegian island is it illegal to die?",
        "answer": "Svalbard Island -- Dying was first banned in 1950 due to frigid temperatures preventing the decomposition of bodies in the local cemetery."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where in the world can you find the most ATMs per capita?",
        "answer": "Macau -- It is a gambling destination that`s seven times greater than Las Vegas. It is also the most densely populated region in the world."
    },
    {
        "question": "What country does the poinsettia plant come from?",
        "answer": "Mexico -- In the 19th century, U.S. ambassador to Mexico, Dr. Joel Roberts Poinsett, discovered the plant in southern Mexico. It is named after him."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the oldest rainforest in the world?",
        "answer": "Daintree rainforest -- Located in Australia, it is 180 million-years-old. By contrast, the Amazon rainforest is only 55 million-years-old."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which ancient landmark was originally known as Cecropia?",
        "answer": "The Acropolis of Athens -- The word \u201cacropolis\u201d translates to high city, but in ancient times the site was instead known by the name Cecropia \u2014 after the city`s mythical first king, Cecrops."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only nation that borders both Pakistan and Bangladesh?",
        "answer": "India"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only nation that borders both Israel and Libya?",
        "answer": "Egypt"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only nation that borders both Uruguay and Venezuela?",
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only nation that borders both Belgium and Spain?",
        "answer": "France"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only nation that borders both Burma and Malaysia?",
        "answer": "Thailand"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the only nation that borders both Costa Rica and Honduras?",
        "answer": "Nicaragua"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US State flag has a Union Jack Flag on it?",
        "answer": "Hawaii"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of the US state of Kentucky?",
        "answer": "Frankfort"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which European city is famous for its Latin Quarter?",
        "answer": "Paris "
    },
    {
        "question": "Lilongwe is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Malawi"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Malawi?",
        "answer": "Lilongwe"
    },
    {
        "question": "What major mountain ranges are located in New York State?",
        "answer": "Adirondack, Catskill, and Appalachian Mountains"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country was the worlds first ice hotel built?",
        "answer": "Sweden"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country borders both North Korea and Finland?",
        "answer": "Russia"
    },
    {
        "question": "The first U.S. state park was created in which state?",
        "answer": "New York"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what US state is the Naismith Memorial Basketball Hall of Fame located?",
        "answer": "Massachusetts"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what city is the Kentucky Derby held?",
        "answer": "Louisville"
    },
    {
        "question": "When measured from its underwater base, what is the tallest mountain?",
        "answer": "Mauna Kea"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Shakespeare`s play, `Romeo and Juliet,` where did Romeo and Juliet live?",
        "answer": "Verona, Italy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which U.S. city`s signature dish is chili over spaghetti with cheese?",
        "answer": "Cincinnati -- It can be a bit sweet in addition to spicy, featuring cinnamon, allspice, cloves, chili powder, cumin and oregano."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which U.S. capital city is the only one with no McDonalds?",
        "answer": "Montpelier, Vermont"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the second-largest Portuguese-speaking nation in population and area?",
        "answer": "Angola"
    },
    {
        "question": "Scotland`s Shetland Islands are home to what geographical point?",
        "answer": "Northernmost point in the U.K. -- They are just 400 miles from the Arctic Circle?"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is nicknamed the `Tar Heel State`?",
        "answer": "North Carolina"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state`s highest mountain is Mt. Rainier?",
        "answer": "Washington"
    }
]